And that's why, no matter what Mommy says..
而那就是為什麼不管媽咪說什麼…
we really were on a break. Yes, we were.
我們都真的暫時分手了 是的，沒錯…
Yes, we were. Come here, gorgeous.
是的，沒錯 來吧，漂亮寶貝
Look at you. You are the cutest little baby ever.
瞧瞧你 你是史上最可愛的小嬰兒了
You're just a little-bitty baby, you know that? But you've got..
你只是個小不丁點嬰兒 你知道嗎？但是你擁有…
You've got big, beautiful eyes.
你擁有大大漂亮的雙眼
Yes, you do. And a.. And a big, round belly.
是的，你有，還有… 還有大大圓圓的肚肚
Big baby butt.
大大的嬰兒屁屁
I like big butts.
我喜歡大屁屁
Oh, my God, Emma. You're laughing.
喔，天啊，艾□你在笑
Oh, my God. You've never done that before, have you?
喔，我的天，你從沒有這樣過，對嗎？
You've never done that before. Daddy made you laugh, huh?
你從來沒有這樣過 爹地逗你笑了，對吧？
Well, Daddy and Sir Mix-A-Lot.
嗯，是爹地還有混音老爹
What? What? You wanna hear some more?
什麼？什麼？ 你還想聽更多是嗎？
I'm a terrible father.
我真是個糟糕的父親
The One With Rosss Inappropriate Song
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- What do you know about investments? - How come?
-你們懂得投資嗎？ -怎麼了？
I'm starting to make good money on the show, and I should do something with it.
我的演出開始讓我賺到一些錢了 所以我想我應該好好利用那些錢
- What do you do with your money now? - It's taped to the back of my toilet tank.
-那你現在是把錢放在哪裡呢？ -藏在我家馬桶水箱後面
I didn't say that. It's in a bank guarded by robots.
我沒有那樣說 是放在銀行由機器人看守著
- Do you have any ideas? - A guy at work got me excited..
-你有什麼想法嗎？ -有個同事的提議讓我覺得很興奮…
about going in on an emu farm. That'd be kind of cool, huh?
是關於投資鴯鳥農場 很酷吧？
Pitching in on the weekends, helping to plant the emus.
在週末的時候過去幫忙 幫助種植鴯鳥
Joe, emus are birds. You raise them for meat.
喬伊，鴯鳥是鳥類 是養來當食物的
Yeah. Right!
嗯，是喔！
People eat birds. Bird meat.
人類會吃小鳥，小鳥肉
Do they just fly into your mouth? Or you go in a restaurant and say:
他們是直接飛進你的嘴裡嗎？ 還是你可以到餐廳說：
"Excuse me, I'll have a bucket of fried bird."
「不好意思，我要點一份炸鳥」
Or maybe just a wing. Or a..
或是一個翅膀，或是…
You should consider something a little less risky.
你應該考慮比較低風險性的投資
I think real estate is your best investment.
我認為房地產會是最好的投資
The Fed just lowered the rates, and the interest on your mortgage is deductible.
聯邦儲備銀行才剛降息 而且房貸的利率也可以扣減所得稅額
That's right. I know some stuff.
沒錯，我懂投資
Real estate, huh?
房地產，是嗎？
And you know who's selling a great apartment? Richard!
你知道誰要賣一間 很棒的公寓嗎？李察！
And you know whose knowledge of her ex-boyfriend is shocking? Monica!
你知道誰對她前男朋友的熟悉度 很嚇人嗎？摩妮卡！
- My dad told me. They play golf together. - Well, maybe I'll join them sometime.
-我爸告訴我的，他們一起打高爾夫球 -那麼或許我應該加入他們
I just hope the club doesn't slip out of my hand..
我只希望球桿不要滑出我的手…
and beat the mustache off his face.
然後把他的八字鬍從他臉上打掉
And then the doctor said Emma has doubled her birth weight..
然後醫生說艾□的體重 已經是出生時的一倍了…
she is in the 90th percentile and she's gonna start eating solid foods soon.
她比百分之九十的嬰兒快 很快就可以吃固體食物了
- That's great! - I know!
-太棒了！ -我知道！
- What did we used to talk about? - No idea.
-我們以前都在談什麼呢？ -不知道
Hi! You have to help me pick a dress. I'm meeting Mike's parents tonight.
嗨！你們要幫我選衣服 我今晚要跟麥克的父母見面
Wow, the boyfriend's parents. That's a big step.
哇，男朋友的父母親，真是一大步
- Really? That hadn't occurred to me. - They'll love you. Just be yourself.
-真的嗎？我倒是沒有這樣想過 -他們會喜歡你的，自然隨性就好
They live on the Upper East Side on Park Avenue.
他們住在上東區的公園大道
Yeah, she can't be herself.
那她就不能自然隨性了
Okay, so, all right, which dress?
好了，那麼，哪一件呢？
- You can say neither. - Oh, God. Neither.
-你們可以說都不好 -喔，天啊，都不好
You can say it nicely.
你們大可以委婉一點說
I'm sorry. We'll take you shopping. It'll be fine.
我很抱歉，我們會帶你去買衣服 沒事的
You are in such good hands, and I am so good with meeting parents.
我會照顧你的 我很會搞跟父母親見面這種事
With the father, you wanna flirt a little, but not in a gross way.
面對他父親，稍微打情罵俏一下 但是不要太過火
Just kind of like, "Mr. Pinzer, I can see where Wallace gets his good looks."
有像是「品瑟先生，我現在終於知道 華勒斯帥氣的長相是遺傳誰的了」
- You went out with Wallace Pinzer? - He took the SATs for me.
-你跟華勒斯品瑟交往過？ -他代替我考聯考
- I knew you didn't get a 1400! - Yeah, well, duh! I mean..
-我就知道你沒有考過高標！ -是啊，哈！我們說的是我耶…
So now, what about with Mike's mom?
那麥克的媽怎麼辦呢？
Well, with the mother, just constantly tell her how amazing her son is.
至於他母親，只要不斷的告訴她 她兒子有多棒就行了
Take it from me. Moms love me. Ross' mom one time actually said..
舉我為例，母親們都很喜歡我 羅斯的媽有一次甚至還說…
I am like the daughter that she never had.
我就像是那個她從未有過的女兒
- She said what? - She's like the daughter she never had.
-她說什麼？ -她就像是那個她從未有過的女兒
Listen.
聽著
I just got Phoebe all dressed to meet Mike's parents.
我才幫菲比打扮好讓她去見麥克的父母
She's so nervous. It's so sweet.
她好緊張，真是太感人了
Guess what. I made Emma laugh today.
猜猜怎麼了，我今天逗艾□笑了
You what? And I missed it..
你什麼？而我竟然錯過…
because I was giving a makeover to that stupid hippie?!
都是因為要幫那 愚蠢的嬉皮改變造型？
Yeah, and it was like a real little person laugh too.
是啊，而且就像是小大人的笑喔！
It was like:
就像是…
Only not creepy.
只不過不像這樣嚇人
- What did you do to make her laugh? - I..
-你做了什麼逗她笑？ -我…
Well, I sang. Actually..
嗯，我唱了歌 其實…
I rapped..
是饒舌歌…
"Baby Got Back."
「寶貝，你的馬達真正」
You what?
你什麼？
You sang to our baby daughter..
你對著我們的寶貝女兒唱…
a song about a guy who likes to have sex..
一首關於男人想要跟巨大屁股女人…
with women with giant asses?
上床的歌？
You know what, if you think about it..
你知道嗎？如果你仔細想想…
it actually promotes a healthy body image..
它事實上是在提倡健康的身體觀念…
because even big butts..
因為即使是大屁股…
or "juicy doubles" are..
或是「可口多汁的雙頰」都是…
Please don't take her away from me.
請不要把她從我身邊帶走
Hi, come on in. I'm Catherine, the listing agent.
嗨，請進 我是凱瑟琳，仲介商
Hi, I'm Joey. This is Chandler.
嗨，我是喬伊，這是錢德
So how come Richard's selling the place? Went bankrupt?
為什麼李察要賣掉這地方呢？ 破產了嗎？
Medical malpractice? Choked on his own mustache?
醫療誤診？被自己的鬍子噎死嗎？
He's buying a much bigger place. It's got a great view of Central Park..
他要買一間更大的公寓 景觀很棒，可以看到中央公園…
That's enough out of you.
你說夠了！
Is there anything we should know about the place?
這地方有什麼我們應該要知道的嗎？
All the appliances are included. There's a lot of light, a new kitchen.
電器用品全部都包含 光線充足，還有新的廚房
I think you guys would be very happy here.
我想你們倆住在這裡一定會很快樂
No, we're not together. We're definitely not a couple.
不，我們沒有在一起 我們絕對不是一對
- Okay. Sorry. - That's all right.
-好的，抱歉 -沒關係
Wow, you seemed pretty insulted by that.
哇，你看起來好像是被侮辱了一樣
What, I'm not good enough for you?
是怎樣？我配不上你嗎？
We are not gonna have this conversation again.
我們不要再討論這個問題了
Look at this place. Why am I so intimidated by this guy?
瞧瞧這地方 我為什麼備受這傢伙的威脅呢？
Pretentious art. This huge, macho couch.
矯情的藝術品，這張大又陽剛的沙發
When we know all he does is sit around..
我們知道他只會坐在那邊…
crying about losing Monica to a real man.
哭泣著為什麼摩妮卡會離開他 而投入一個真正男人的懷抱
- You don't think he's here, do you? - I don't know.
-他應該不在這裡吧，對嗎？ -我不知道
It's a nice place, but I gotta say, I don't know if I see myself living here.
這是個好地方，但是我必須要說 我不知道我能不能住得習慣
Well, let me see.
嗯，讓我們來試試看
Yeah, I can see it.
是的，我可以住得習慣
Look at these videos. I mean, who does he think he is?
瞧瞧這些錄影帶 他以為他是誰啊？
Magnum Force, Dirty Harry, Cool Hand Luke.
《辣手神探追魂槍》、《緊急追捕令》 《鐵窗喋血》
- Oh, my God. - What?
-喔，我的天 -怎麼了？
There's a tape here with Monica's name on it.
有一卷帶子上面有摩妮卡的名字
A tape with a girl's name on it. It's probably a sex tape.
有一卷帶子上面有女生的名字 可能是性愛綠影帶
Wait a minute.
等一下
This says "Monica."
上面寫著「摩妮卡」…
And this is Richard's apartment.
而且這裡是李察的公寓
Get there faster!
快點想！
Wow. You look..
哇，你看起來…
like my mom.
真像我媽
I'm wearing pantyhose.
我有穿絲襪
- Great! Come on in. - Okay.
-太棒了！請進 -好的
Thank you.
謝謝
- Oh, my God. You're rich. - No, my parents are rich.
-喔，我的天，你真有錢 -不，是我父母親有錢
Well, so? They gotta die someday. Hello!
喔，那又如何呢？他們有天也會死的 哈囉！
Mom, Dad, this is Phoebe.
爸媽，這是菲比
Phoebe, these are my parents, Theodore and Bitsy.
菲比，他們是我父母 希爾多跟貝西
Theodore, Bitsy..
希爾多，貝西…
what a delight.
很高興能與你們見面
- It's so nice to finally meet you. - And you.
-終於見到你真是太高興了 -我也是
Your home is lovely.
你們家真是美好
Thank you. I'll give you a tour later. It's actually three floors.
謝謝，等一下我可以帶你參觀 這裡其實有三層樓
Holy crap!
媽媽咪啊！
Why don't you come meet our friends.
過來認識我們的朋友吧！
Try and stop me.
試試擋我看看
- What are you doing? - Trying to get your parents to like me.
-你在做什麼呢？ -試著讓你父母親喜歡我
I'm sure they will, but you don't have to do this.
我相信他們會的，但是你不用這樣假
I want them to get to know Phoebe, not "Phoebe."
我要他們認識菲比，不是「妃妣」
It is fun, though, isn't it?
不過很好玩，不是嗎？
- You've got it. - All right.
-知道了 -好了
It's hard to stop.
很難停止
Well, come on.
好了，來吧
Phoebe, these are our friends Tom and Sue Engel.
菲比，這是我們的朋友 湯姆跟蘇安格
Phoebe, come sit. Tell us a little bit about yourself.
菲比，來坐下 跟我們介紹一下你自己
- So where are you from? - Okay.
-你是哪裡人呢？ -好的
Well, all right. Originally, I'm from upstate..
嗯，好的，我本來是上州人…
but then my mom killed herself, and my stepdad went to prison.
但是後來我媽自殺，然後繼父去坐牢
So I moved to the city, where I lived in a burned-out Buick LeSabre for a while.
所以我就搬到市中心 住在一輛火燒車裡一陣子
Which was okay. That was okay.
那倒是沒關係，還好啦
Until I got hepatitis, you know..
直到我染上肝炎，你知道的…
because this pimp spit in my mouth and..
因為有個壞蛋吐口水到我嘴裡然後…
But I got over it.
但是我已經好了
And, anyway, now I'm a freelance massage therapist..
然後，反正現在我是 自由按摩治療師…
which isn't always steady money, but at least I don't pay taxes.
賺的錢不是很穩固，但至少不用繳稅
So where does everyone summer?
那大家都到哪度暑假呢？
I'm not gonna watch it. I don't need to watch it.
我不會看的，我不需要看
I mean, what good could possibly come from watching it?
我是說，看了又有什麼好處呢？
Well, we know I'm gonna watch it.
嗯，我們知道我還是要看
- Hey, dude, what's up? - Don't judge me! I'm only human!
-嘿，兄弟，怎麼了？ -別審判我！我只不過是個普通人！
Did you take that tape?
你拿走那卷帶子嗎？
I had to! Imagine you were married and you found a tape of your wife..
我必須要！假設你結婚了 然後你發現一卷你老婆帶子…
in another guy's apartment. Wouldn't you need to know what was on it?
在另一個男人的公寓裡 你難道不想知道裡面是什麼嗎？
I don't know. Who am I married to?
我不知道，我跟誰結婚呢？
Some girl.
某個女孩子
She hot?
她辣嗎？
How did she get me to settle down?
她是怎麼讓我定下來的？
All right, I'm gonna watch it.
好了，我要看
I mean, it's probably not even what I think it is.
我是說，或許根本不是我想的那樣
Even if it is, it can't possibly be as bad as what I'm picturing in my head.
即使是，或許也不像我在腦海中 想像的情景那樣糟糕
Can it?
會嗎？
In my experience, if a girl says yes to being taped..
依據我的經驗 如果女生答應可以錄下來…
she doesn't say no to much else, I'll tell you.
其它的也就都不會拒絕了 我跟你說
- Then you have to watch it for me. - What?
-那你先幫我看 -什麼？
Just for a few seconds so I can know what it is. Please?
幾秒鐘就好，讓我知道那是什麼，拜託
All right, fine. But if I enjoy this, you have only yourself to blame!
好啦，可以，但是萬一我很樂在其中 你就只能怪你自己！
- Why am I hearing cheering? - It's okay. It's just a football game.
-為什麼我聽到歡呼聲？ -沒關係，是足球賽
- It's just football? - You were all worried for nothing.
-只是足球賽？ -你擔心是多餘的
It's football! It's just football!
是足球！只是足球！
This is great! This is the first time I've ever enjoyed football!
太棒了！這是我第一次真正喜歡足球！
I think it may be customary to get a beer.
我想這時候喝啤酒很對味
What the..?
搞什麼…？
- What are you doing? - You don't wanna see what I just saw!
-你在做什麼？ -你不想要看到我剛看到的東西！
What are you guys doing?
你們在做什麼？
Oh, my God! Is that Richard?
喔，我的天！那是李察嗎？
- Oh, God, this is not going well. - No, you're doing fine. Really.
-喔，天啊，真是進行的不順利 -不，你做的很好，真的
- Why don't you go talk to my dad. - Okay, okay, okay.
-你何不去找我爸聊聊 -好，好的，好的
- Still sure about me being myself? - Absolutely.
-還確定要我做我自己嗎？ -當然
Though maybe just a little less "pimp spit."
或許少說一些「壞蛋吐口水」的事
So, Theodore, I can see where Mike gets his good looks from.
希爾多，我現在知道麥克的帥氣外表 是遺傳自誰的了
Well..
嗯…
- You must work out all the time. - Not all the time. I do the best I can.
-你一定經常做運動 -不是很常，不過我盡量
Yeah, I bet. Look out!
是啊，我想也是，看招！
- Oh, my God. Are you okay? - I recently had surgery.
-喔，我的天，你還好嗎？ -我最近剛動完手術
- I'm so sorry. - No, I'll be fine.
-我很抱歉 -沒關係，我沒事
- I just should check the stitches. - I really am sorry.
-我只是應該要去檢查一下傷口 -我真的很抱歉
How could you know? Why wouldn't you punch me in the stomach?
你怎麼會知道呢？ 為什麼你不會打我肚子呢？
Did you just hit my dad?
你剛剛是不是打了我爸？
Yes. I'm sorry. I've never met a boyfriend's parents before.
是的，我很抱歉 我從來沒有見過男朋友的父母親
But, I mean, you have met humans before, right?
但是，你總該有見過人，對嗎？
Why don't you go talk to my mom.
你何不去找我媽聊聊
Okay, yeah, your mom. She looks nice. I can talk to her.
好的，你媽，她看起來很和善 我可以跟她聊的
You do that, and I'm gonna go check my dad for signs of internal bleeding.
你去聊吧！ 我要去看看我爸是不是有內出血的現象
Bitsy? Listen, I wanted to thank you again for having me here tonight.
貝西，我想要再次謝謝你 邀請我今晚過來
Well, not at all.
喔，不用客氣
Also, I just want you to know what a wonderful man your son is.
還有，我只想讓你知道 你兒子是個很棒的男人
- Thank you. I think so too. - It's a testament to how he was raised.
-謝謝，我也這麼認為 -一切都是他受了良好的家庭教育
Especially to you, because he's very respectful of women.
尤其是你的功勞 因為他十分尊重女性
- Is he really? - He is so considerate of my feelings.
-他真的嗎？ -他非常體貼我的感受
You know, I think you'd also like to know that he is a very gentle lover.
我認為你也會想知道 他是個非常溫柔的愛人
Excuse me?
什麼？
No, don't get me wrong. No, not in like a sissy way.
不，別誤會我 不，不是那種娘娘腔的樣子
When he gets going..
當他瘋起來的時候…
he can rattle a headboard like a sailor on leave.
他可是像休假的船員一樣神勇
That's.. my boy.
那就是…我兒子
Awesome.
酷斃了
Okay, please laugh for Mommy. Please?
好了，幫媽咪笑一笑 拜託
Please laugh for Mommy.
請為媽咪笑一個
Not funny, huh?
不好笑，對吧？
Well, so is it..
嗯，所以是不是…
only offensive novelty rap?
只有低級好玩的饒舌歌才行呢？
Or maybe just, you know, rap in general. Because Mommy can rap.
或是或許只要是饒舌歌都行 因為媽咪會饒舌喔
I can't rap.
我不會饒舌
All right, sweetheart. This is only because I love you so much.
好了，親愛的，這只是因為我太愛你了
And I know that you're not gonna tell anybody.
而且我知道你不會告訴別人
Emma, you're laughing! You are!
艾□，你在笑！你笑了！
You really do like big butts, don't you?
你真的很喜歡大屁股，對不對？
You beautiful little weirdo.
你這個漂亮的小怪蛋
You missed it! She was laughing!
你錯過了！她剛剛在笑！
It was amazing.
真是不可思議
It was amazing. It was the most beautiful, beautiful sound.
是很不可思議，那就像是最美妙的聲音
I know, isn't it? What'd you do to get her to laugh?
我知道，可不是嗎？ 你做了什麼逗她笑？
You know, I just.. A couple of things I tried. Different..
你知道的，我只不過… 試了一些東西，不同的…
Just sang a little "The Itsy-Bitsy Spider."
只是唱了一點「癢癢小蜘蛛」
You sang "Baby Got Back, " didn't you?
你唱了「寶貝，你的馬達真正」 對不對？
Nothing else worked! That girl is all about the ass!
其它的方法都沒有用！ 這女孩就是喜歡屁屁！
And then it goes back to the chorus.
然後再回到主旋律
Resolve. And that's the end of the song.
然後那就是歌曲的結尾
I realize you hadn't asked to hear it..
我知道你們沒有要我唱…
but no one had spoken in 17 minutes.
但是已經有十七分鐘沒有人說話了
Phoebe writes lots of songs. What was that one you sang the other night?
菲比創作了許多歌曲 你那天晚上唱的歌是什麼呢？
"Pervert Parade"?
《變態遊行》嗎？
- "Ode to a Pubic Hair"? - Stop.
-《陰毛頌》嗎？ -停止
Oh, God. Is that veal?
喔，天啊，這是小牛肉嗎？
Mom, I thought I told you, Phoebe's a vegetarian.
媽，我以為我跟你說過菲比是素食者
No, that's okay. That's okay. I mean, I am a vegetarian..
不，沒關係，沒關係 我是說，我是素食者…
except for veal. Yeah. No. Veal I love.
不過我吃小牛肉 是的，我愛吃小牛肉
- Phoebe, you don't have to eat that. - Any baby animals. Kittens, fish babies.
-菲比，你可以不用吃的 -我喜歡任何小動物食物，小貓，小魚
But, you know, especially veal.
但是，尤其喜歡小牛肉
You know, and this nice vein of fat running through it.
這上面還有帶一點很棒的肥肉
Yummy.
好吃
So..
那…
what do you think?
你們覺得如何呢？
So you stole that tape from Richard's apartment?
所以你從李察的公寓偷了這卷帶子？
Listen to the judgment from the porn star!
聽聽這三級片脫星在批評我！
That tape was never meant to be seen by..
那帶子本來就不是要讓…
Joey, I would feel more comfortable if this conversation were in private.
喬伊，我希望可以私下談論這件事
Monica, look, I don't think you and I have any secrets anymore.
摩妮卡，聽著，我不認為 你我之間有存在任何秘密了
Not ready to joke about it yet? See you later.
還沒有準備好可以開玩笑嗎？待會見
Why in the world would you take this tape? And why would you watch it?
你為什麼要拿這卷帶子呢？ 而且為什麼要看呢？
Because that's who I am. Okay?
因為我就是這樣的人，好嗎？
I'm sure a man like Richard could see a tape like that and not be bothered.
我相信像李察那樣的男人可以 看這樣的帶子而且不會被說教
It'd just be another saucy anecdote..
這只不過是個黃色的小插曲…
for him to share at his men's club over brandy and mustaches.
讓他可以在他的男性俱樂部裡 邊喝著白蘭地摸著鬍子和兄弟們分享
Is all of this about you not being able to grow a mustache?
這一切跟你沒有辦法長鬍子有關嗎？
This is about you and Richard. He's clearly not over you.
這跟你還有李察有關 很明顯地他還沒有忘記你
He keeps a tape so he can look at it whenever he wants.
他保留這帶子讓他可以 在任何想的時候就看
Isn't that sad? Can't you see how pathetic that is?
那不是很悲慘嗎？ 你看不出來這是多可悲的事嗎？
Don't be jealous. You should feel bad for him.
別吃醋了，你應該為他感到可憐
Yeah, well, poor Richard, he..
是啊，可憐的李察，他…
I can grow a mustache.
我可以長鬍子的
This is not our problem. We have each other. That's all that matters.
這不是我們的問題，我們擁有彼此 這是最重要的
But I just keep picturing you rolling around with him, with your..
但是我就是忘不了你滾在他身邊 穿著你的…
cowboy boots in the air.
牛仔靴子在空中晃來晃去
Cowboy boots? I've never worn cowboy boots in my whole life.
牛仔靴子？我這輩子 從沒有穿過牛仔靴子
Good, good. Play more because I wanna see how it ends.
很好，非常好，再多放一點 因為我想看結局是怎樣
- That's not me! - What?
-那不是我！ -什麼？
That's not you! Life is good again!
那不是你！美好的生命 又再度來臨了！
Ride 'em, cowgirl!
騎上去，牛仔女！
That bastard taped over me!
那渾蛋錄了別人在我的帶子上！
Is that a problem?
那有什麼問題嗎？
It's just so insulting. Spring for a new blank tape, doctor!
真是太侮辱人了 花錢買新的空白帶子嘛，醫師！
Yes, but the important thing is that we have each other, right?
是的，但是重要的是我們擁有彼此 不是嗎？
Well, yeah. It's just so rude!
嗯，是的，不過這非常沒禮貌！
- And the way we did it was a lot better.. - Are you going to finish that sentence?
-我們做的方式要比那個好太多… -你要把這個句子說完嗎？
I can't imagine what he sees in her.
我無法想像他在她身上 看到什麼吸引人的
She actually makes me miss that pill-popping ex-wife of his.
她還真讓我懷念起他那嗑藥的前妻
Hello, dear.
哈囉，親愛的
- What's going on? - We were just chitchatting.
-怎麼了？ -我們只是在隨便聊聊
- How's your friend? - A little better.
-你的朋友還好嗎？ -有好一點了
Do you know who's moving back into town? Tom and Sue's daughter, Jen.
你知道誰要搬回城裡了嗎？ 湯姆跟蘇的女兒，珍
You remember her, Michael. She's lovely, well-behaved and single.
你記得她的，麥克 她很可愛，行為舉止端莊，而且單身
- I'm not interested. - Please, darling, let's be honest.
-我沒有興趣 -拜託，親愛的，我們老實說
You can have all the sailor fun you want with that one.
你跟那個也可以享受像船員般的樂趣的
- But let's be real. - All right, stop.
-但是我們要面對現實 -好了，停
All Phoebe has done is try and get you to like her. Maybe it's not clear..
菲比所做的一切都是為了要讓 你們喜歡她，或許不是很明顯…
but she did her best.
但是她已經盡力而為了
- She's a little different than you are. - Michael, a pimp spit in her mouth.
-她是跟你們有點不同 -麥克，一個壞蛋吐口水在她嘴裡
So what? If I can get past that, it shouldn't bother you.
那又如何？如果我都無所謂了 你們有什麼好在乎的
You don't have to like her. Just accept the fact that I do.
你們沒有必要去喜歡她 只需要接受我喜歡她的事實就可以
If you can't even be civil to the woman I love..
如果你們無法對我愛的女人…
- The woman you what? - Yeah, the woman you what?
-你什麼的女人？ -是啊，你什麼的女人？
The woman I love.
我愛的女人
I love you.
我愛你
Something I shouldn't say for the first time, in front of my parents..
我不該當我父母面前 第一次說這種話
and Tom and Sue.
還有湯姆跟蘇面前
Who are, by the way, the most sinfully boring people I've ever met in my life.
對了，他們是我一生中 遇過最無聊的人
- I love you too. - You do?
-我也愛你 -真的？
How great is this?
很棒嗎？
Wanna get out of here?
想要離開這裡嗎？
- Mom, Dad. Thanks for dinner. - I had a great time.
-爸媽，謝謝你們的晚餐 -我很開心
It was really top-drawer. And here's something rich.
這裡真的很高級，而且更棒的是…
Thirteen bathrooms in this place, I threw up in the coat closet.
這裡有十三間浴室 但是我吐在衣帽間裡面
Ta-ta!
拜了！
One more time from the top!
從頭再來一次！
Rachel, please! That is so inappropriate!
瑞秋，拜託！ 這實在太不恰當了！